Guide to the David Russell Perry Alphabetical Files, 1917-1976
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
David Russell Perry Alphabetical Files 1917-1976 (Bulk 1955-1970)
Perry, David Russell
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Durham, North Carolina 27708-0185
perry
Language: English.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Biographical Note
David Russell Perry is a physician at Watts Hospital (Durham, N.C.) and Coroner of Durham County. He is also an alumnus of Wake Forest University and Jefferson Medical College.
Collection Overview
Pertains to Perry's career as a general practitioner on the staff of Watts hospital (Durham, N.C.), Coroner of Durham County, and his affiliations with several service organizations. They include the American Legion (Durham, N.C.), Temple Baptist Church (Durham, N.C.), Baptist Hospitals, Inc., Yates Baptist Association, and the alumni associations of Campbell College, Wake Forest University, and Jefferson Medical College in Philadelphia. Perry was also a member of the Durham Sports and Recreation Committee.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Durham Chamber of Commerce. Sports and Recreation Committee.; Jefferson Medical College -- Alumni.; Wake Forest University -- Alumni.; Campbell College (Buies Creek, N.C.)--Alumni.; American Legion (Durham, N.C.).; Baptist Hositals, Inc.; Yates Baptist Association.; Physicians -- North Carolina.
Contents of Collection
- Alphabetical Files Series
  - American Legion, 1936-1976 (Box 1)
  - Campbell College, 1912-1975, (3 folders)
  - Coroners and Medical Examiners of N.C., 1953-1972
  - Correspondence, Financial Papers, Family Clippings, 1937-1976, undated
  - Durham and Durham County, 1953-1974
  - Durham Chamber of Commerce Sports and Recreation Committee, 1955-1975
  - Durham Sports Enterprises, Inc., 1937-1967
  - Durham-Orange County Medical Society and N.C. State Medical Society, 1930-1973 (Box 2)
  - Jefferson Medical College, 1930-1976
  - Lincoln Hospital, 1948-1967
  - North Carolina Baptist Hospitals, Inc., 1950-1969, (7 folders)
  - North Carolina Baptist Hospitals, Inc., 1970-1973, (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - North Carolina Baptist State Convention, 1946-1975, (2 folders)
  - Temple Baptist Church, Durham, NC 1953-1973, (2 folders)
  - Wake Forest College, 1942-1952, (2 folders)
  - Wake Forest College/University, 1953-1975, undated, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Watts Hospital, 1933-1975
  - Yates Baptist Association, 1958-1974, (4 folders)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977-1980
- Oversize Material
  - Correspondence, Financial Papers, Family Clippings, 1937-1976, undated (Oversize-box 15)